RESUME

Name:Gandem Anil Kumar

Contact No: 8247251313

8185046271

e- mail: gandem.anilkumar@gmail.com

1. Academic Qualifications:

S No	Examination	Board/University	Specialization	Year	Division/
					%Marks
1	Ph.D.	AU College of	Soil Mechanics and	_	Pursuing
		Engineering	Foundation Engineering		
2	M.Tech	NIT Rourkela	Transportation	2015	8.55
IVI. I ech		NII Kourkeia	Engineering	2013	0.33
3	B. Tech,	Acharya Nagarjuna			
	Civil	University	Civil Engineering	2012	66.5%
	Engineering	Oniversity			
4	Intermediate/	BIE, Andhra	M.P.C	2008	85.4%
	+2	Pradesh	WI.I .C	2006	03.470
6	SSC	BSE, Andhra	SSC	2006	76%
		Pradesh	SSC	2000	7070

2. Professional Experience:

S No	Designation	Place of Work	Period
1	Asst. Professor	AITAM, Tekkali	01-07-2015 to 30-09-2019
2.	Village surveyor	Ragolu-2, Srikakulam	02-10-2019 to till date

3. Fields of Research Interests:

- Improvement of strength properties of expensive soils by using plastic waste in the form of Fibers, geosynthetics, HDPE &LDPE.
- Desiccation cracking behavior of fiber reinforced soils.
- Improvement of sub-base, base course in Pavements by using recycled asphalt aggregates.
- Capacity and Level of service (LOS) Study in urban roads for safe movement of vehicles.

• Analysis of stability of slopes & Soil bearing capacity by using Finite element analysis (PLAXIS).

4. Memberships:

- 1. Indian Geotechnical Society (**IGS**) Life Member.
- 2. Indian Society for Technical Education (ISTE) Life member.

5. Academic Profile:

- **1. Specialization**: Ph.D.---- Soil Mechanics and Foundation Engineering M.Tech Transportation Engineering
- 2. Titles of the Thesis Work in my academic career:
- B.Tech: CBR STUDIES ON EXPANSIVE SOILS USING STABILIZED RICE HUSK ASH CUSHION [B.Tech]

Guided by Dr. M. Rama Rao

Nov '11 - Apr '12

The importance of this project is to improve the strength characteristics of the expansive soil as it tends to swell and shrink due to climatic changes and also change due to ground water table. In this process we use rice husk ash and lime as a stabilized material to the soil and improve the strength properties, CBR.

• PEDESTRIAN FLOW BEHAVIOUR ALONG SIDEWALKS [M.Tech]

Guided by Dr. Ujjal chattaraj

June '14 – Apr '15

In this project the main theme is to find the pedestrian characteristics like speed, flow, density, distance headway and fundamental diagrams of these combinations and also finding effect of pedestrian characteristics due to unidirectional flow and bidirectional flow.

3. Publications:

• Comparision of Compressive strength of M25, M30 Grades Of Concrete By Partially Replacement Of Fly Ash Nominal And Accelerated Curing. Published in IJIRT-journal volume 3 issue 1 june 2016.

6. Project Works Guided For B.E. (Civil-Engineering students):

S.No	Title of the Project work	Year	
1	Utilization of HDPE strips as a reinforcing material for improvement of	2017-2018	
	expensive soils in construction of flexible pavement		
2	Mixed Vehicles Flow Behaviour Along Mid-Block sections in urban	2017-2018	
	roads		
3	Model flexible pavement design on Reinforced Expensive soil subgrade	2018-2019	
4	A Study on Index Properties and Engineering Properties of fiber	2018-2019	
	reinforced Expensive soils		

7. Seminars/ Conferences/Workshops Participated:

- Active participation in IGC-2009 (Indian Geotechnical Conference) conducted in RVR&JC College, Guntur.
- Participation in one day workshop on "problems and adversities in geotechnical engineering practice and solutions" (PAGES) conducted in Vignan University.
- Active participation in International Workshop on **REIMAGINE STEM** conducted in AITAM collage, Tekkali.
- Participated in one day awareness Programme on "Intellectual Property Rights" organized by R&D cell AITAM, Tekkali.
- Participated in TEQIP-II sponsored one-week national workshop on "RECENT DEVELOPMENTS IN STRUCTURAL ENGINEERING" organized by AITAM collage, Tekkali.
- Participated in one day awareness Programme on "Intellectual Property Rights & Innovations" organized by R&D cell AITAM, Tekkali.
- Participated in the national seminar on "RECENT INNOVATIONS IN CIVIL ENGINEERING" organized by AITAM collage, Tekkali.
- Participated in one day awareness Programme on "Intellectual Property Rights And Patents" organized by R&D cell AITAM, Tekkali.
- Participated in the workshop on "GOOD CONSTRUCTION PRACTICES" organized by department of civil engineering, Andhra University College of engineering, Visakhapatnam.
- Participated training Programme on "Earthquake Risk Mitigation and Management" organized NIDM in collaboration with department of civil engineering, Andhra University, Visakhapatnam.

8. Social Commitments:

• Actively participated to help the people at the time of covid pandemic situation in rehabilitation centers and covid vaccination centers.

9. Personal Profile:

Father's Name : GANDEM SATYAM

Mother's name : G.Leelavathi
Date of birth : 01-07-1991
Marital Status : Married
Nationality : Indian

Address : waltair (Vill & Post)

Santhakaviti (Mandal) Srikakulam (Dist) Andhra Pradesh

532168

I hereby declare that all the above written particulars are true to the best of my knowledge and can refer above for verification.

Place:	Gandem Anil kumar
Date:	